<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Simon Vadsholt</title>
    <link>https://simonvadsholt.dk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Simon Vadsholt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://simonvadsholt.dk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://simonvadsholt.dk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonvadsholt.dk/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Simon Vadsholt, a recent graduate in Computer Science &amp;amp; Economics. Below are some of my interests and ongoing projects, all of which will hopefully be covered more fully on here at some point. If you&amp;rsquo;re in a postion to hire people to do cool things, take a look at my CV&#xA;Projects TabletopTunes TabletopTunes came to be because I got tired of juggling too many Youtube playlists of ambient mood music while running TTRPGs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meditations on the mainframe</title>
      <link>https://simonvadsholt.dk/mainframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonvadsholt.dk/mainframe/</guid>
      <description>Since learning that mainframes are still very much in use in financial IT, where throughput and availability are paramount, I have taken an interest in the work on those machines. As few hobbyists have access to their own mainframe, such an interest also necessarily involves the work of emulating a markedly different machine architecture on your personal computer and getting an OS very much of the 70s running on it. In the modern world where there is a 5-step Medium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obscure Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://simonvadsholt.dk/search-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonvadsholt.dk/search-engines/</guid>
      <description>The web was built for serendipity. Yet as the digital garden has become a shopping mall, those delightful moments of stumbling upon exactly what you needed (or didn&amp;rsquo;t know you needed) are fading. Here, I&amp;rsquo;ve gathered a few search engines that still enable digital serendipity.&#xA;Marginalia search.marginalia.nu is probably the entry on this list closest to a standard search engine, the big difference being the exclusion of commercial sites. This leads to search results consisting of passion rather than profit motive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
