<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Effective Altruism Denmark</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1314/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Effective Altruism Denmark</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1314/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EA is three radical ideas I want to protect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/blog/ea-three-radical-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/blog/ea-three-radical-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editor&amp;rsquo;s Note: What follows is a brief excerpt from Peter&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive article. For the full narrative and in-depth exploration, please &lt;a href=&#34;https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/posts/MP9qDZCXMaTJhiJ9u/ea-is-three-radical-ideas-i-want-to-protect&#34;&gt;click here to read the complete post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Essentially, effective altruism contains three radical ideas that I don&amp;rsquo;t easily find in other communities. These three ideas are ideas I want to protect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;radical-empathy&#34;&gt;Radical empathy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Humanity has long had a fairly narrow moral circle. &lt;a href=&#34;https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/posts/ehZK259et52Xnvw5F/radical-empathy&#34;&gt;Radical Empathy&lt;/a&gt; is the idea that there are many groups of people, or other entities, that are worthy of moral concern even if they don&amp;rsquo;t look or act like us. Moreover, it&amp;rsquo;s important to deliberately identify all entities worthy of moral concern so that we can ensure they are protected. I find effective altruism to be unique in extending moral concern to not just traditionally neglected farm animals and future humans (very important) &amp;ndash; but also to &lt;a href=&#34;https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/posts/T5fSphiK6sQ6hyptX/opinion-estimating-invertebrate-sentience&#34;&gt;invertebrates&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://80000hours.org/problem-profiles/artificial-sentience/&#34;&gt;potential digital minds&lt;/a&gt;. Effective altruists are also unique in trying to intentionally understand who might matter and why and actually incorporating this into the process of discovering how to best help the world. Asking the question &amp;ldquo;Who might matter that we currently neglect?&amp;rdquo; is a key question that is asked way too rarely.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snakebites kill 100,000 people every year, here&#39;s what you should know</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/blog/snakebites-kill-100000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/blog/snakebites-kill-100000/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editors note: this is a cross-post from Mathias&amp;rsquo; &lt;a href=&#34;https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/posts/WyqGircJgCBG9ivNL/snakebites-kill-100-000-people-every-year-here-s-what-you&#34;&gt;EA Forum post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WHO estimates between 81,000-138,000 die every year from venomous snakebites. What on earth!? When I first heard this I refused to believe it. How had I managed to call myself an EA for so many years and not known snakebites were this big a deal? Not only do snakebites kill an unfathomable number of people, another four hundred thousand are permanently disabled every year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
